

Geatriz David

Rua Padre António Vieira, n4 2740-113 Porto Salvo, Lisboa +351 912015817 beatrizdavid\_c@hotmail.com

#### BIOGRAPHY

I'm a 24 year old potuguese designer. I have work experience in different countries and different areas. I love to travel, read and create. I also have a growing passion for photography and fashion. Former scout and horse rider, knitting enthusiast and part-time watercolorist, I'm always in pursuit of something new to learn.

**Bē** /beatrizcdavid

in /beatrizcdavid

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## LEAD DESIGNER

Brandhunters | July 2020 - Today

Providing Graphic, Web Design and Social Media Content services for big brands in the automotive industry, such as Volkswagen, Audi and Skoda, amongst others.

#### GRAPHIC AND WEB DESIGNER

Parceiro Digital | April 2019 - December 2019

Graphic and web design work in a marketing agency, based in São Paulo, Brazil.

## COLUMNIST

Nuba DX - Nuba Mags | May 2018 - December 2019

Writing articles about new up-and-coming designers and innovative products, with a main focus on sustainability.

### COSTUMER CARE AGENT

Residentas | February - May 2018

Providing costumer care services in luxury apartments in Lisbon, I was in constant communication with clients from all over the world, and was responsible for check-ins and chek-outs.

# **EDUCATION**

### PgD IN BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

Fundação Getúlio Vargas | 2018 - 2019

I finished my post-graduation course in business management in December 2019, expanding my knowledge in a completely different area of study.

#### EXCHANGE PROGRAM

Universidade Presbeteriana Mackenzie |2016

I did my Exchange experience in São Paulo Brazil, where I was able to learn different design concepts and methods.

# LICENCIATE DEGREE IN DESIGN

Faculdade de Arquitetura de Lisboa | 2014 - 2017

I finished my licenciate degree in Lisbon in December 2017, I had the possibility to explore different areas of Design, such as product, graphic, editorial, interior, and others.

### IELTS ACADEMIC CERTIFICATE

Overall Band Score: 8.0

CEFR Level: C1

# LANGUAGE SKILLS





SPANISH 50%



# SKILLS

Illustrator	
Photoshop	_
Indesign	
Office	
Adobe XD	-
Sketchup	
Lightroom	_
InVision	